function questionnaire(count = 10) {
    const qA = [{
        question: "How many continents are there?",
        option: ["11", "9", "7", "6"],
        answer: "7"
    },

    {
        question: "What is the capital of Austria?",
        option: ["Budapest", "Vienna", "Helsinki", "Venice"],
        answer: "Vienna"
    },

    {
        question: "Which country is Bucharest located?",
        option: ["UAE", "Canada", "Portugal", "Romania"],
        answer: "Romania"
    },

    {
        question: "Where is mount Everest located?",
        option: ["Kenya", "Spain", "Nepal", "Hawai"],
        answer: "Nepal"
    },

    {
        question: "The name of the longest River in the world is?",
        option: ["Mississippi", "Nile", "Yangzte", "Ganges"],
            answer: "Nile"
        },

        {
            question: "Which of these countries belonged to the former USSR?",
            option: ["Niger", "Russia", "Belgium", "England"],
            answer: "Russia"
        },

        {
            question: "Which of the following cities lies on the GMT?",
            option: ["Yaounde", "Lagos", "London", "Ankara"],
            answer: "London"
        },

        {
            question: "Where is the Grand Canyon located?",
            option: ["Utah", "Texas", "Arizona", "California"],
            answer: "Arizona"
        },

        {
            question: "Olympus Mons is the name of a mountain located in which of these planets?",
            option: ["Mars", "Earth", "Venus", "Neptune"],
            answer: "Mars"
        },
        {
            question: "Which of the following countries lies on GMT?",
            option: ["Algeria", "Ghana", "Tunisia", "Lesotho"],
            answer: "Ghana"
        },

        {
            question: "The name of the largest River in the world in terms of volume is?",
            option: ["Niger", "Limpopo", "Amazon", "Nile"],
            answer: "Amazon"
        },


        {
            question: "The highest mountain on Earth is named, Mount?",
            option: ["Everest", "Kilimanjaro", "Kilau", "Pele"],
            answer: "Everest"
        },


        {
            question: "One of the following is not a type of rainfall",
            option: ["Convectional", "Orogenic", "Beach", "Relief"],
            answer: "Beach"
        },
        {
            question: "One of the following is not a type of climate",
            option: ["Typhoon", "Mediterranean", "Temperate", "Tropical"],
            answer: "Typhoon"
        },

        {
            question: "All the following is a type of season except?",
            option: ["Fall", "Winter", "Harmattan", "Sunny"],
            answer: "Sunny"
        },

        {
            question: "All the following is a type of natural disaster except?",
            option: ["Flooding", "Tsunami", "Earthquacke", "Hurricane"],
            answer: "Earthquacke"
        },



        {
            question: "The Prime Latitude is called?",
            option: ["Tropics of Cancer", "Artic Circle", "Equator", "Lat"],
            answer: "Equator"
        },
        {
            question: "Which of the following rocks is formed from magma?",
            option: ["Granite", "Shale", "Limestone", "Marble"],
            answer: "Granite"
        },

        {
            question: "Which of these is caused by wind action?",
            option: ["Butte", "Cliff", "Stalagmite", "Karst"],
            answer: "Butte"
        },

        {
            question: "Which of the below is formed at the late stage of a river?",
            option: ["V shaped Valley", "Rapids and Cataract", "Ox-Bow Lake", "Delta"],
            answer: "Delta"
        },



        {
            question: "Which of the countries below is the largest in land mass?",
            option: ["Canada", "China", "Russia", "India"],
            answer: "Russia"
        },
        {
            question: "Which of the below is not a continent?",
            option: ["Africa", "USA", "Austalia", "Europe"],
            answer: "USA"
        },


        {
            question: "A place where the Water Table intersects the surface in a desert is called?",
            option: ["Well", "Stream", "Oasis", "River"],
            answer: "Oasis"
        },

        {
            question: "Sandstorm is a feature of what type of vegetation belt?",
            option: ["Rain Forest", "Mangroove", "Desert", "Guinea Savannah"],
            answer: "Desert"
        }


    ]
    return (
        qA.sort(() => { return (Math.random() - Math.random()) }).slice(0, count)
    )

}
export default questionnaire;

